This is the world that feeds the Swiss Banks’ Octopus.
Questo è il mondo che nutre la piovra della Banca Svizzera.
This is the world where too much is not enough.
Questo è il mondo in cui il troppo non è abbastanza.
This is the world where negativity is a plus.
Questo è il mondo in cui la negatività è considerata un vantaggio.
This is the world where the saints say: “Enough”.
Questo è il mondo in cui i santi dicono basta.
1. This is a world where 1.3 billion people
1. Questo è un mondo in cui un miliardo e trecento milioni di persone
live on an income of less than $1 a day
vivono con un reddito inferiore ad un dollaro al giorno
and where the planet does not have enough natural resources
ed in cui il pianeta non ha sufficienti risorse naturali
to sustain, at a worldwide scale, the consumption pattern
per sostenere su scala mondiale i modelli di consumo
of Malaysia, leave alone America.
della Malesia, per non parlare dell’America.
PLEASE SHRI DURGA,
SHRI DURGA, PER FAVORE,
DESTROY THE EVIL FORCES THAT MATERIALISM CREATED.
DISTRUGGI LE FORZE MALVAGIE CREATE DAL MATERIALISMO.
Om Twameva Sakshat
Om Twameva Sakshat
Shri Durga Namoh Namaha.
Shri Durga Namoh Namaha.
2. This is a world where ten per cent of world trade
2. Questo è un mondo in cui il dieci per cento del commercio globale
is generated by drugs and narco-traffics, or US$100 billion
è costituito da droghe e narcotraffico, e ammonta a 100 miliardi di dollari
represents the amount that yearly poisons mankind,
la cifra che annualmente avvelena l’umanità;
while money laundering in Switzerland and elsewhere
mentre il riciclaggio di denaro in Svizzera e altrove
has become a most prosperous activity,
è diventata una attività estremamente redditizia
reaching all levels of society.
che tocca tutti i livelli nella società.
PLEASE SHRI RAKTABIJA VINASHINI,
SHRI RAKTABIJA VINASHINI, PER FAVORE,
DESTROY THE EVIL FORCES THAT MATERIALISM CREATED.
DISTRUGGI LE FORZE MALVAGIE CREATE DAL MATERIALISMO.
Om Twameva Sakshat
Om Twameva Sakshat
Shri Raktabija Vinashini Namoh Namaha.
Shri Raktabija Vinashini Namoh Namaha.
3. This is a world where Wall Street sucks the wealth
3. Questo è un mondo in cui Wall Street sottrae la ricchezza
from the working middle class to bestow it upon the rich
dei lavoratori del ceto medio per assegnarla ai ricchi,
and where Walt Disney makes you forget all about it.
ed in cui Walt Disney fa dimenticare tutto questo.
PLEASE SHRI KATYAYANI,
SHRI KATYAYANI, PER FAVORE,
DESTROY THE EVIL FORCES THAT MATERIALISM CREATED.
DISTRUGGI LE FORZE MALVAGIE CREATE DAL MATERIALISMO.
Om Twameva Sakshat
Om Twameva Sakshat
Shri Katyayani Namoh Namaha.
Shri Katyayani Namoh Namaha.
4. This is a world where an Egyptian eats at MacDonalds in Cairo
4. Questo è un mondo in cui un egiziano mangia da MacDonalds al Cairo
and a Chinese at Pizza Hut in Beijing, because modern consumerism
ed un cinese da Pizza Hut a Pechino, poiché il consumismo moderno
expresses the lowest common denominator of world culture
esprime il minimo comune denominatore della cultura mondiale
and erases the meaning of national values and traditions.
e cancella il significato di valori e tradizioni nazionali.
PLEASE SHRI SHAKAMBARI,
SHRI SHAKAMBARI, PER FAVORE,
DESTROY THE EVIL FORCES THAT MATERIALISM CREATED.
DISTRUGGI LE FORZE MALVAGIE CREATE DAL MATERIALISMO.
Om Twameva Sakshat
Om Twameva Sakshat
Shri Shakambari Namoh Namaha.
Shri Shakambari Namoh Namaha.
5. The new multinational entities are experimenting with new forms
5. Le nuove realtà multinazionali stanno sperimentando nuove forme di dittatura,
reducing to slavery a subdued working class
riducendo in schiavitù una classe operaia sottomessa
and exploiting children on the altar of productivity gains.
e sfruttando bambini sull’altare dei profitti produttivi.
PLEASE SHRI RAKSHAKARI,
SHRI RAKSHAKARI, PER FAVORE,
DESTROY THE EVIL FORCES THAT MATERIALISM CREATED.
DISTRUGGI LE FORZE MALVAGIE CREATE DAL MATERIALISMO.
Om Twameva Sakshat
Om Twameva Sakshat
Shri Rakshakari Namoh Namaha.
Shri Rakshakari Namoh Namaha.
6. The globalization of production and services allow a few global players
6. La globalizzazione di produzione e servizi consente a pochi giocatori mondiali
to befool us and impose the rules of their game
di ingannarci e di imporre le loro regole del gioco
to the mass of unsuspecting consumers.
alla massa di ignari consumatori.
PLEASE SHRI BHIMADEVI,
SHRI BHIMADEVI, PER FAVORE,
DESTROY THE EVIL FORCES THAT MATERIALISM CREATED.
DISTRUGGI LE FORZE MALVAGIE CREATE DAL MATERIALISMO.
Om Twameva Sakshat
Om Twameva Sakshat
Shri Bhimadevi Namoh Namaha.
Shri Bhimadevi Namoh Namaha.
7. Vast restructuration endeavours are progressively leading
7. Grandi sforzi di ristrutturazione stanno portando progressivamente
to the eradication of small and medium-sized enterprises
allo sradicamento di piccole e medie imprese
for the benefit of gigantic corporations operating on a worldwide scale.
a vantaggio di enormi società che operano su scala mondiale.
PLEASE SHRI CHANDIKA,
SHRI CHANDIKA, PER FAVORE,
DESTROY THE EVIL FORCES THAT MATERIALISM CREATED.
DISTRUGGI LE FORZE MALVAGIE CREATE DAL MATERIALISMO.
Om Twameva Sakshat
Om Twameva Sakshat
Shri Chandika Namoh Namaha.
Shri Chandika Namoh Namaha.
8. The gradual concentration of liquid wealth in the hands of the super rich
8. La graduale concentrazione di denaro liquido nella mani dei magnati
is marginalizing national sovereignty and its elected officials,
marginalizza la sovranità nazionale e i suoi funzionari eletti,
and is imposing a titanic dimension to the ruler-ship of money.
ed impone una dimensione titanica al dominio del denaro.
PLEASE SHRI RAKSHASAGNI,
SHRI RAKSHASAGNI, PER FAVORE,
DESTROY THE EVIL FORCES THAT MATERIALISM CREATED.
DISTRUGGI LE FORZE MALVAGIE CREATE DAL MATERIALISMO.
Om Twameva Sakshat
Om Twameva Sakshat
Shri Rakshasagni Namoh Namaha.
Shri Rakshasagni Namoh Namaha.
9. Greed raised to the power 108
9. L’avidità elevata alla 108° potenza
means the pauperization of the world’s middle class
provoca l’impoverimento della classe media mondiale
and outrageous wealth for the remaining 10%.
ed una oltraggiosa ricchezza per il restante 10%.
PLEASE SHRI DAITYENDRA MARDINI,
SHRI DAITYENDRA MARDINI, PER FAVORE,
DESTROY THE EVIL FORCES THAT MATERIALISM CREATED.
DISTRUGGI LE FORZE MALVAGIE CREATE DAL MATERIALISMO.
Om Twameva Sakshat
Om Twameva Sakshat
Shri Daityendra Mardini Namoh Namaha.
Shri Daityendra Mardini Namoh Namaha.
10. The systematic elimination of alternative economic solutions,
10. L’eliminazione sistematica di soluzioni economiche alternative,
unequal trade and financial manipulations are challenging
il commercio iniquo e le manipolazioni finanziarie
PLEASE SHRI VAJRINI,
SHRI VAJRINI, PER FAVORE,
DESTROY THE EVIL FORCES THAT MATERIALISM CREATED.
DISTRUGGI LE FORZE MALVAGIE CREATE DAL MATERIALISMO.
Om Twameva Sakshat
Om Twameva Sakshat
Shri Vajrini Namoh Namaha.
Shri Vajrini Namoh Namaha.
11. The deregulation of the financial markets has opened wide the gates
11. La deregolamentazione dei mercati finanziari ha spalancato i cancelli
of Jurassic Park for the large financial predators to roam about
di Jurassic Park alle scorribande dei grandi predatori finanziari
and thousands of billions of dollars are created from nothing by speculators
e gli speculatori creano dal niente migliaia di miliardi di dollari
to feed their unlimited thirst for money and power.
per soddisfare la loro sete illimitata di denaro e potere.
PLEASE SHRI UGRACHANDESHWARI,
SHRI UGRACHANDESHWARI, PER FAVORE,
DESTROY THE EVIL FORCES THAT MATERIALISM CREATED.
DISTRUGGI LE FORZE MALVAGIE CREATE DAL MATERIALISMO.
Om Twameva Sakshat
Om Twameva Sakshat
Shri Ugrachandeshwari Namoh Namaha.
Shri Ugrachandeshwari Namoh Namaha.
12. The Swiss financial centre works as a haven for rich tax-dodgers
12. Il centro finanziario svizzero è un rifugio sicuro per i ricchi evasori fiscali
from developing countries, and diverts needed capital
dai Paesi in via di sviluppo, che dirotta capitali necessari
from national investment programmes, industrial infrastructures
ai programmi nazionali di investimento, alle infrastrutture industriali
and social expenditure to inflate the stock exchange of the developed countries.
e alla spesa sociale, e gonfia le borse valori dei Paesi sviluppati.
PLEASE SHRI UGRAPRABHA,
SHRI UGRAPRABHA, PER FAVORE,
DESTROY THE EVIL FORCES THAT MATERIALISM CREATED.
DISTRUGGI LE FORZE MALVAGIE CREATE DAL MATERIALISMO.
Om Twameva Sakshat
Om Twameva Sakshat
Shri Ugraprabha Namoh Namaha.
Shri Ugraprabha Namoh Namaha.
13. The trend of today’s mega mergers is to marginalize the State,
13. La tendenza delle attuali grandi fusioni è di marginalizzare lo Stato,
bypass national legislation, manipulate the market,
aggirare la legislazione nazionale, manipolare il mercato,
control the economy and, for all practical purposes,
controllare l’economia e, in pratica,
finish off the social foundations of real democracy.
distruggere le fondamenta sociali della vera democrazia.
PLEASE SHRI MAHAKALI,
SHRI MAHAKALI, PER FAVORE,
DESTROY THE EVIL FORCES THAT MATERIALISM CREATED.
DISTRUGGI LE FORZE MALVAGIE CREATE DAL MATERIALISMO.
Om Twameva Sakshat
Om Twameva Sakshat
Shri Mahakali Namoh Namaha.
Shri Mahakali Namoh Namaha.
14. The lure and mirage of such a radical concentration of wealth
14.La lusinga ed il miraggio di una simile radicale concentrazione di ricchezza
and power threatens to neutralize all seeking of the Spirit,
e potere, minaccia di neutralizzare ogni ricerca dello Spirito
and the deafening roar of the triumph of asuric materialism
ed il fragore assordante di trionfo del materialismo “asurico”
destroys the hope of millions of seekers.
distrugge la speranza di milioni di ricercatori.
PLEASE SHRI MAHAMAYA,
SHRI MAHAMAYA, PER FAVORE,
DESTROY THE EVIL FORCES THAT MATERIALISM CREATED.
DISTRUGGI LE FORZE MALVAGIE CREATE DAL MATERIALISMO.
Om Twameva Sakshat
Om Twameva Sakshat
Shri Mahamaya Namoh Namaha.
Shri Mahamaya Namoh Namaha.
15. The alliance of mafia, secretive bankers and corrupt managers
15. L’alleanza di mafia, banchieri reticenti e manager corrotti
has infiltrated the world economy and is threatening the ethics of collectivity
si è infiltrata nell’economia mondiale e minaccia l’etica della collettività,
which provides the foundation for the value system of our entire civilization.
su cui si fonda il sistema di valori della nostra intera civiltà.
PLEASE SHRI VIRATANGANA,
SHRI VIRATANGANA, PER FAVORE,
DESTROY THE EVIL FORCES THAT MATERIALISM CREATED.
DISTRUGGI LE FORZE MALVAGIE CREATE DAL MATERIALISMO.
Om Twameva Sakshat
Om Twameva Sakshat
Shri Viratangana Namoh Namaha.
Shri Viratangana Namoh Namaha.
16. The enormous increase of financial assets has siphoned cash money
16. L’enorme incremento di beni finanziari ha sottratto denaro contante
out of the real economy and channeled it into the financial markets,
all’economia reale immettendolo nei mercati finanziari
building up a planetary gambling casino
e costruendo così un casinò di giochi d’azzardo planetario
where arbitrary currency speculation can mount
in cui la speculazione valutaria arbitraria può sferrare
huge attacks against any country which tries to follow socially-minded policies.
attacchi immani contro qualsiasi Paese cerchi di seguire politiche sociali.
PLEASE SHRI KHADGAPALINI,
SHRI KHADGAPALINI, PER FAVORE,
DESTROY THE EVIL FORCES THAT MATERIALISM CREATED.
DISTRUGGI LE FORZE MALVAGIE CREATE DAL MATERIALISMO.
Om Twameva Sakshat
Om Twameva Sakshat
Shri Khadgapalini Namoh Namaha.
Shri Khadgapalini Namoh Namaha.
17. The etheric sophistication of financial electronic circuits has created
17. La sofisticazione eterica dei circuiti finanziari elettronici ha creato
a virtual world where the immateriality of money has become the sole reality.
un mondo virtuale in cui l’immaterialità del denaro è diventata l’unica realtà.
PLEASE SHRI VISHNUMAYA,
SHRI VISHNUMAYA, PER FAVORE,
DESTROY THE EVIL FORCES THAT MATERIALISM CREATED.
DISTRUGGI LE FORZE MALVAGIE CREATE DAL MATERIALISMO.
Om Twameva Sakshat
Om Twameva Sakshat
Shri Vishnumaya Namoh Namaha.
Shri Vishnumaya Namoh Namaha.
18. The progressive domination of technology
18. La progressiva dominazione della tecnologia
is sucking the blood of the farmer, the artist and the potter,
succhia il sangue dell’agricoltore, dell’artista e dell’artigiano,
turning the man who works with his hands into a permanently handicapped person.
trasformando chi lavora con le mani in una persona permanentemente svantaggiata.
PLEASE SHRI DEVA KARYA SAMUDYATA,
SHRI DEVA KARYA SAMUDYATA, PER FAVORE,
DESTROY THE EVIL FORCES THAT MATERIALISM CREATED.
DISTRUGGI LE FORZE MALVAGIE CREATE DAL MATERIALISMO.
Om Twameva Sakshat
Om Twameva Sakshat
Shri Deva Karya Samudyata Namoh Namaha.
Shri Deva Karya Samudyata Namoh Namaha.
19. The information highway leads to the maya web of a virtual world
19. La moderna tecnologia dell’informazione crea la rete illusoria di un mondo virtuale
where human attention is scattered, desire is confused,
in cui l’attenzione umana si disperde, il desiderio è confuso,
truth is atomized and the soul is thereby reduced to slavery.
la verità è disintegrata e l’anima è pertanto ridotta in schiavitù.
PLEASE SHRI RADHA,
SHRI RADHA, PER FAVORE,
DESTROY THE EVIL FORCES THAT MATERIALISM CREATED.
DISTRUGGI LE FORZE MALVAGIE CREATE DAL MATERIALISMO.
Om Twameva Sakshat
Om Twameva Sakshat
Shri Radha Namoh Namaha.
Shri Radha Namoh Namaha.
20. Modern communication can become a domestic [may that mean “demonic”] tool
20. La moderna rete di comunicazione può diventare uno strumento demoniaco
in the hands of a few media moguls and opinion-making tycoons
nelle mani di pochi magnati dei media e opinionisti influenti
which are spreading their hedonistic world views of power, money and sex.
i quali diffondono la loro visione del mondo edonistica
PLEASE SHRI SHUKRATMIKA,
SHRI SHUKRATMIKA, PER FAVORE,
DESTROY THE EVIL FORCES THAT MATERIALISM CREATED.
DISTRUGGI LE FORZE MALVAGIE CREATE DAL MATERIALISMO.
Om Twameva Sakshat
Om Twameva Sakshat
Shri Shukratmika Namoh Namaha.
Shri Shukratmika Namoh Namaha.
21. The Mlechas of Satan have infiltrated the Internet global village
21. I Mlechas di Satana si sono infiltrati nel villaggio globale di Internet
to pour pornographic dirt and filth within the nest
per riversare immoralità e oscenità pornografiche all’interno del nido
of the family and to spread hell’s shadows in the minds of helpless people.
della famiglia e per diffondere ombre infernali nelle menti di gente indifesa.
PLEASE SHRI NIRMALA KUMARI,
SHRI NIRMALA KUMARI, PER FAVORE,
DESTROY THE EVIL FORCES THAT MATERIALISM CREATED.
DISTRUGGI LE FORZE MALVAGIE CREATE DAL MATERIALISMO.
Om Twameva Sakshat
Om Twameva Sakshat
Shri Nirmala Kumari Namoh Namaha.
Shri Nirmala Kumari Namoh Namaha.
Hail, salutations to the great Devi! Aum, Amen.
Ave, Omaggio alla Grande Devi! Aum, Amen.
May there be Auspiciousness, Joy and Peace.
Possano esservi buon auspicio, gioia e pace.
May Thy Divine grace penetrate the waters
Possa la Tua grazia divina permeare le acque
flowing from our mountains to the four corners of Europe
che scorrono dalle nostre montagne ai quattro angoli dell’Europa
and spread the pure vibrations of the Aquarian Age.
e diffondere le vibrazioni pure dell’Età dell’Acquario!
Salutations to Thee Shri Mataji Nirmala Devi Ji,
Omaggio a Te, Shri Mataji Nirmala Devi Ji, Splendente, formidabile Avatar!
We bow to Thee, most pleasing yet most frightful,
Noi ci inchiniamo a Te, la più amabile ancorché la più temibile,
who has been approached by the Trimurtis for the sake of protecting the universe.
alla quale la Trimurti si rivolse per la protezione dell’universo.
Today, in this festival of Navaratri,
Oggi, in questa celebrazione di Navaratri,
we chant the litany of Thy children in Switzerland
recitiamo la preghiera dei Tuoi figli svizzeri
for the defeat of the foes of the Spirit,
per la sconfitta dei nemici dello Spirito,
and we offer to Thy glittering teeth the new asuric forms of materialism.
ed offriamo ai Tuoi denti scintillanti le nuove forme “asuriche” del materialismo.
PLEASE SHRI RAKTADANTIKA,
SHRI RAKTADANTIKA, PER FAVORE,
DESTROY THE EVIL FORCES THAT MATERIALISM CREATED.
DISTRUGGI LE FORZE MALVAGIE CREATE DAL MATERIALISMO.
Om Twameva Sakshat
Om Twameva Sakshat
Shri Kalki Sakshat
Shri Kalki Sakshat
Shri Sahastrara Swamini
Shri Sahastrara Swamini
Moksha Pradayini Mataji
Moksha Pradayini Mataji
Shri Nirmala Devyai Namoh Namaha.
Shri Nirmala Devyai Namoh Namaha.